var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "وَأَبًّا",
        "answer": "and grass",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-abban",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبِيهِ",
        "answer": "and his father",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "wa-abīhi",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخِيهِ",
        "answer": "his brother",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "akhīhi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "But when",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "452",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "730",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَرَهُ",
        "answer": "He commanded him",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "amarahu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمِّهِ",
        "answer": "And his mother",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wa-ummihi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَّا",
        "answer": "As for",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But as for",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "the man",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرَرَةٍ",
        "answer": "dutiful",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "bararatin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَبْشِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "rejoicing at good news",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "mus'tabshiratun",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَنِيهِ",
        "answer": "and his children",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "wabanīhi",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُ",
        "answer": "came to him",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "jāahu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكَ",
        "answer": "came to you",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "jāaka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتِ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "jāati",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبًّا",
        "answer": "grain",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "ḥabban",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَدَائِقَ",
        "answer": "And gardens",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waḥadāiqa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَىٰ",
        "answer": "fears",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yakhshā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَهُ",
        "answer": "He created him",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "khalaqahu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَهُ",
        "answer": "He created him",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "khalaqahu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُدْرِيكَ",
        "answer": "would make you know",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yud'rīka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَكَرَهُ",
        "answer": "may remember it",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "dhakarahu",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذَّكَّرُ",
        "answer": "be reminded",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "yadhakkaru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the reminder",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "l-dhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذْكِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a reminder",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "tadhkiratun",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْفُوعَةٍ",
        "answer": "Exalted",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "marfūʿatin",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْهَقُهَا",
        "answer": "Will cover them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tarhaquhā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزَّكَّىٰ",
        "answer": "purify himself",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yazzakkā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزَّكَّىٰ",
        "answer": "he purifies himself",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yazzakkā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَيْتُونًا",
        "answer": "And olive",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wazaytūnan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلَ",
        "answer": "the way",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "l-sabīla",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "striving",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yasʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفَرَةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) scribes",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "safaratin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْفِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) bright",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "mus'firatun",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَأْنٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a matter",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "shanun",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَقَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We cleaved",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shaqaqnā",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَقًّا",
        "answer": "splitting",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "shaqqan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "516",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَبْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] poured",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣababnā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبًّا",
        "answer": "(in) abundance",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣabban",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَاحِبَتِهِ",
        "answer": "And his wife",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "waṣāḥibatihi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُحُفٍ",
        "answer": "sheets",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣuḥufin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّاخَّةُ",
        "answer": "the Deafening Blast",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ṣākhatu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصَدَّىٰ",
        "answer": "give attention",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taṣaddā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَاحِكَةٌ",
        "answer": "Laughing",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ḍāḥikatun",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامِهِ",
        "answer": "his food",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmihi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُطَهَّرَةٍ",
        "answer": "purified",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "muṭahharatin",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَبَسَ",
        "answer": "He frowned",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿabasa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْمَىٰ",
        "answer": "the blind man",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-aʿmā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِنَبًا",
        "answer": "And grapes",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waʿinaban",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَبَرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) dust",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ghabaratun",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُلْبًا",
        "answer": "(of) thick foliage",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ghul'ban",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُغْنِيهِ",
        "answer": "occupying him",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yugh'nīhi",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَغْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "considers himself free from need",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "is'taghnā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَجَرَةُ",
        "answer": "the wicked ones",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-fajaratu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفِرُّ",
        "answer": "will flee",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yafirru",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَاكِهَةً",
        "answer": "And fruits",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wafākihatan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَقْبَرَهُ",
        "answer": "and provides a grave for him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-aqbarahu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَرَةٌ",
        "answer": "darkness",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "qataratun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُتِلَ",
        "answer": "Is destroyed",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "qutila",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَدَّرَهُ",
        "answer": "then He proportioned him",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "faqaddarahu",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَضْبًا",
        "answer": "and green fodder",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waqaḍban",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْضِ",
        "answer": "he has accomplished",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yaqḍi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِرَامٍ",
        "answer": "Noble",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "kirāmin",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُكَرَّمَةٍ",
        "answer": "honored",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "mukarramatin",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْفَرَهُ",
        "answer": "ungrateful is he",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "akfarahu",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَفَرَةُ",
        "answer": "(are) the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "l-kafaratu",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "For every",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَلَهَّىٰ",
        "answer": "(are) distracted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "talahhā",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعًا",
        "answer": "(As) a provision",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "matāʿan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "امْرِئٍ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "im'ri-in",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَرْءُ",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-maru",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَاتَهُ",
        "answer": "He causes him to die",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "amātahu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the water",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-māa",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْبَتْنَا",
        "answer": "Then We caused to grow",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "fa-anbatnā",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَخْلًا",
        "answer": "and date-palms",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wanakhlan",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَرَهُ",
        "answer": "He will resurrect him",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ansharahu",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُطْفَةٍ",
        "answer": "a semen-drop",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "nuṭ'fatin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَنْظُرِ",
        "answer": "Then let look",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "falyanẓuri",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِأَنْعَامِكُمْ",
        "answer": "and for your cattle",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "wali-anʿāmikum",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَنْفَعَهُ",
        "answer": "so would benefit him",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "fatanfaʿahu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهٌ",
        "answer": "Faces",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "wujūhun",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوُجُوهٌ",
        "answer": "And faces",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "wawujūhun",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "and turned away",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "watawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَيْدِي",
        "answer": "In (the) hands",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "bi-aydī",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسَّرَهُ",
        "answer": "He made easy for him",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yassarahu",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "80",
        "ayah": "34"
    }
]; 
export default words;